JAMAINE ROSEBOROUGH

JUNIOR DATA SCIENTIST

(Active Secret Clearance /w TS Eligibility)

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Efficiently ambitious U.S Marine Corps Veteran and Computer Science major currently attending Palomar College, with 5 years of experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of Python programming, Machine learning, and Data analytic skills to successfully fill the Junior Data Scientist role at your company. Frequently praised as dependable by my peers, I can be relied upon to provide relevant value to your team.

EXPERIENCE

DATA SCIENCE STUDENT

CNM Ingenuity Deep Dive Coding, Vista, CA / Sep 2021 - Present

Building upon a prior Python skillset with Data Science through exploring, studying, and building Machine Learning models to include Linear Regression, Decision Trees, Random Forests, Bagging, and Boosting.

LOGISTICS CHIEF

United States Marine Corps, Camp Pendleton, CA / Feb 2017 - Present

Focusing on the more Data rich aspect of my role serving as the Embarkation Clerk (September 2017-June 2019), Embarkation NCO (June 2019-May 2020), and Embarkation Chief (May 2020-September 2021) of the 1st MLG (Marine Logistics Group), I utilized an enterprise data storage system (ICODES) which I complimented with my Python knowledge, utilizing Spyder to create scripts that pulls and organizes logistical data from our enterprise system in order to improve workflow as well as maintain ITV of U.S Military assets. I've also conducted logistical inspections of the entire 1st Marine Logistics Group where I received multiple awards for my thoroughness and efficiency.

DATA INTERN

Duro UAS, New York, NY / Jun 2016 - Nov 2016

As a data intern at Duro UAS, I was able to build my skills in data sourcing, data manipulation, and data visualization. I worked with data from OSHA as well as data from multiple open sources. I was also able to share my knowledge through mentoring prospective Python programmers from High School students to adults.

PYTHON PROGRAMMING STUDENT

The Knowledge House, New York, NY / Mar 2016 - Jul 2016

Learned the basic principles of Python programming, commonly used packages, as well as building using frameworks such as Flask and Django.

- iroseborough31@gmail.com

 icom

 icom
- (718) 308-1059
- 1275 North Citrus Ave Apt A, Vista, CA, 92083

SKILLS

Machine Learning Models

(Regression, GNB Classifier, Tree based methods, NLP)

Python Programming

SKlearn, Pandas, Numpy, Django & Flask (Python Web Frameworks)

Data Visualization

Matplotlib, Plotly, Seaborn HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Postgres SQL

Data Analysis

GIT

EDUCATION

PALOMAR COLLEGE San Marcos, CA

Associate in Science (A.S.) Computer Science Candidate (Expected graduation Jun 2022)

CERTIFICATIONS

The Knowledge House, Programming with Python